{
    "subject": "resource/Carmine_Galante",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/East_Harlem",
    "human_readable": "Carmine Galante was born in East Harlem.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.895355761051178,
            "question": "Where was Carmine Galante born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808864712715149,
            "question": "What is the significance of East Harlem in relation to Carmine Galante?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7737837433815002,
            "question": "In what century was Carmine Galante born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46462926268577576,
            "question": "What neighborhood is associated with Carmine Galante's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46315327286720276,
            "question": "What is Carmine Galante known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3880007266998291,
            "question": "Was Carmine Galante a prominent figure in his community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27635473012924194,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Carmine Galante's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.260145366191864,
            "question": "Was Carmine Galante involved in organized crime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21268370747566223,
            "question": "What historical events might have influenced Carmine Galante's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13166992366313934,
            "question": "Are there any books or documentaries about Carmine Galante?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carmine Galante was born in East Harlem.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5370_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical events might have influenced Carmine Galante's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5370_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Carmine Galante involved in organized crime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5370_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Carmine Galante's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5370_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5370_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll the documents mention that Carmine Galante was born in East Harlem, so the statement is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Carmine Galante was born in East Harlem.\" Multiple sources mention his birthplace as East Harlem, Manhattan, New York City."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}